{
    "id": "893edff5c3d84bc28fa97a19c3a16591",
    "title": "Sentence improvement",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "fa5782cc57af4723b6929036e4ef445f",
            "title": "Sentence Improvement Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I gave my daughter a ..................... ..",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "beautifully illustrated child’s encyclopedia",
                        "beautifully illustrated children’s encyclopedia",
                        "child’s beautifully illustrated encyclopedia"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Workers who …………………. the same operation day after day take no pleasure or pride in their work.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "perform",
                        "have performed",
                        "had performed"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The popular theory that modern man came out of Africa …………………. into doubt by the discovery of a 3,50,000 year old skull from China.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "have thrown",
                        "have been thrown",
                        "has been thrown",
                        "had been thrown"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The woman looked askance at the tablet and asked if it ……………….. all that was to be given to a patient to make him well.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is",
                        "was",
                        "has been"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The old woman ……………… with a beaming face the next day and reported that her husband had recovered.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "returns",
                        "returned",
                        "has returned",
                        "had returned"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": "5b3c4b47953e4fbba4af3b8ad5c6c31f",
            "title": "Sentence Improvement",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Will you ........................................ dollars in this hour of need?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "lent me few",
                        "lend me a few",
                        "lend me few"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "................................................. understand anything he says.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "A half of his students doesn’t",
                        "Half of his students don’t",
                        "Half his students don’t"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Where ............................................ I lent you?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "are those ten dollars",
                        "is that ten dollars",
                        "are the ten dollars"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "........................................................ for well over twenty years, I am reluctant to move to another city.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Since I have been living in Bangalore",
                        "Since I was living in Bangalore",
                        "Since I had been living in Bangalore"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The boy complained of .................................................... by his step-mother.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "tortured",
                        "having tortured",
                        "having been tortured"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}